Kelly, Edward J. Papers 5867
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Edward J. Kelly Papers
1958-1978
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Kelly, Edward J.
5867
16 cubic feet
16 linear ft.
Papers (documents).
5722548
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 01, 2013
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, April 17, 2019
Biographical / Historical
Kelly was a pilot for United Air Lines and a member of Air Lines Pilot Association Executive Board for many years, in the 1940s and 1950s. He also served on the system board of adjustment.
Scope and Contents
The papers include cases presented before the system board of adjustment and discussions of health benefits for pilots and stewardesses.
Also included are the papers of H.W. Reid, a member of UAL's Master Executive Council in the early 1950s.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 5002: American Association for Social Security Records 5149: Brotherhood of Railroad Trainmen Records 5268: Western Federation of Miners International Mine, Mill and Smelter Workers Records 5478: AFL-CIO Railway Employees' Department Records 5583/3: Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3 5609: Philip Ross Collection of NLRB Documents 5619: ACWA Records 5693: Labor Editorial Files 5743 P: ACWA Photographs
Airlines -- Employees -- Labor unions; Kelly, Edward; United Air Lines, Inc.
5722548
- United Airlines, Inc. Denver Colorado, 1957-1968 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Committee Notes Negotiations and Management Interpretation, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- INT'L Press Information and Agenda Items, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Reports (Various) Air Line Pilots Assoc. Nov. 3-8 1958 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Pertaining to Subeg. 9 Agreement, 1958-1960 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- 1959 Agreement + Letters Of (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Correspondence Member File 1960 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Old Schedule Rules + Runholder Lists, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- FEIA Vs. ALPA- UAL-CAP Arbitration, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- United Airlines, Inc. Chicago Illinois + Air Line Pilots Association, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Lint's Report 1967 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Handbook for ALPA Air Safety Activities and Letters to Executive Committee+ Board of Directors, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Handbook for ALPA Air Safety Activities and Letters to Executive Committee and Board of Directors, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- 1958- NEGOS. (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Thru Flying, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Denver Meeting, 1956-1958 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- UAL MEC Chairman and Senior Copilot Rep. Report, 1956-1959 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- To Members of the Benefits Policy Study Committee, 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- 4/13/ to 4/16/59 milg., 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- MTG. BSC 3/24 25 26/59, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Interim Report 2/18/59, 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- INTRA Committee, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Comm Work (Box 1, Folder 24)
- ALPA Action/ Exec. Comma Bd. Directors, 1957-1959 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Comm From ALPA, 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- By- Laws of the Air Line Pilots Association and Insurance Plan, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Comparative Monthly Benefit Income + Strike benefit Assessment Cost, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Strike Benefit and Assessment Cost Analysis for Benefit Policy Study Committee, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  Scope and Contents
  Don J. Smith and Wallace W. Anderson
- MEC + LEC, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- MEM Letters to ALPA, 1958-1959 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Amendment to Agreement Between United Air Lines, Inc. and ALPA Letters, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Ehlies, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Various ALPA Letters, 1957-1959 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Amendment to Agreement Between United Air Lines, Inc. and the Air Line Pilots, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Compilation of the Actions of the Airline Pilots Association Board of Directors, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- United Air Lines, Inc. Denver Colorado, 1951 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Reading File, 1963-1964 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Air Line Benefit Survey, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Remarks of Allen E. Gramza, Director of the Legal Department ALPA International, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- 1967 Negotiations Seminar Research Materials (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Negotiator's Handbook, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- ALPA Financial Statement, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  Sep. 30, 1960
- Air Line Pilots Association, International Analysis of Costs by Airline and Functions for the Fiscal year ends, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Report of Organizational Structure Study Committee, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  Nov. 14-16, 1960
- Wage + Working Conditions Policy Committee Second Interim Report, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  Feb. 8,1960
- The Need For A Three Man Crew on Jet Transports, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Air Line Pilots Association Compilation of the Actions of the Board of Directors at Thirteenth Biennial Convention, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  Nov. 8-14
- Pilot Opener October 1960 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Pilot Opening Proposal October 1960 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Compilation of the Actions of the Air Line Pilots Association Board of Directors, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  Fifteenth Biennial Convention Nov. 3-9
- NEGOS Interpr, 1965-1968 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- NEGOS Interpr Cont.., 1962-1965 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Labor Info Legislative Statistics, 1965-1968 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Labor Info Legislative Statistics Cont., 1965-1968 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Minutes, Page one, ALPA News Bulletin, Tech Talk, Misc. (Folder 2 of 2), 1966-1967 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Report of Benefit Policy Study Committee, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Exhibits, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Comments by Section- Board (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Extra Letter Comments, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Committee Comments, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Agenda Items, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  Air Line Pilots Association 16th Biennial Convention
- Policy- Benefits Assessments By Laws, 1960 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Report of the Benefit Policy Study Committee, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Report of the Benefit Policy Study Committee, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Report of the Benefit Policy Study Committee, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Report of the Benefit Policy Study Committee, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- In the Matter between the United Airlines Pilots' Merger Committee and Capital Airlines Pilots' Merger Committee, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Flight Engineers, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- In the Matter between the United Air Lines Pilots' Merger Committee and Capital Airlines Pilots' Merger Committee, 1962-1965 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Costa 65, 1965-1970 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Costa 65 65-20, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- PAA. Negotiations 1955 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Grady 65-26, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- System Seniority vs. Down Seniority, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Grady 65-26, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Peate 65-27, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Agreements Other Than U.A.L., 1955 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Peate, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Fitzpatrick 5867, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Agreements Other than VAL, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Fitzpatrick 65-28, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Case No. 65-30 Airline Pilots Association (International) parties G.K. McKean, 1965-1967 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Case No. 65-30 Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parts: G.K. McKean, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Opening Letter to Company, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Case No. 65-31 Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties R.L. Shaumleffel, 1960-1963 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- DC- 7 Arbitration, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Case No. 65-31 Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties: R.L. Shaumleffel, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Case No. 65-32 to 65-48 Air Line Pilots Association, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Case No. 65-32 to 65-48 Air Line Pilots Association, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Co. Negotiations Opening Letters, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Skeen, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Skeen 65-51, 1964-1968 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Expedited Cases Kahn Air Line Pilots Association (International), 1965-1967 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Expedited Cases Gill Air Line Pilots Association (International), 1966 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- ALPA Case No. 6721 and 6653, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Case No. 66-5 Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties R.L. Trembley, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Marshall 66-6, 1965-1967 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- United Air Lines Pilots System Board of Adjustment Board No. 66-9, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- By Laws, Policy Contract, Railway Labor Act, ETC- ALPA, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- 1950's System Board, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Board No. 58-8, 59-6 and 59-70 Decision in Grievance, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- System Board Members, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- 1956 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Gillespie Air Line Pilots Association (International) Cosgrave, R.P. Consolidated with Dardoon, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Case No. Pending Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties, Davidson F.H. Vs. Val, 1956-1957 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties Bos, R.S., 1958 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Case No. April 15 Session '57 Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties Mitchell, W.F., Schwarz, W.F. LEE B.E., 1956 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Case No. Appeal 15' 57 Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties Steidl, J.P., 1956 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Appeal 15 meeting Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties Weber, V.C., 1956 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Case No. April 15, 1957 Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties Bean, O.S., 1956 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Case No. March 15 Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties Myers E.B. Vs. VAL, 1953-1954 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- March 15 Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties Gallion, C.H, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Case No. March 12 Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties Annett, H. 1 + 2 Vs. VAL, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Case No. 5-7-4 Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties J.D. Cook, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Case No. 57-5 Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties J.D. Cook, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Case No. 57-6 Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties John R. Cagney, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Case No. 57-7 Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties O.G. Tierney, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Case No. 57-8 Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties E.N. McKittrick. J.V. Enright, J.M. Hykes, J.J. McCormick, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Case No. 57-9Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties H.M. Chance ET AL, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Case No. 57-10 Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties H.M. Chance- R.H. Anderson, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Case No. 57-11 Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties A. Fernandez et al, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Case No. 57-12 Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties Mullenniex, 1957-1958 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Case No. 57-13 Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties Crasen et al, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Case No. 57-14 Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties Phillip W. Fisher, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- System Board Correspondence, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Case No. 58-3 Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties O.O. Figge, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Case No. 58-1 Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties G.W. Bay, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Case No. 58- 4 Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties J. Taylor (Grievance CHRMN SFO In Behalf of All Pilots), 1959 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Case No. 58-5 Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties HW Estey, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Case No. 58-6 Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties E.N. McKittrick (Grievance CHM IDC.) {W.L. Moore R.W. Boyce E.J. McCormick, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Case No. 58-7 Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties RP Callaghan- RC Jaekel, 1958 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Case No. 58-8 Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties L.F. Higman Vs. Val, 1958-1960 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- System Board Corr. 1959, 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Case No. 59-2 Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties W.V. Grimson Vs. Val, 1959-1960 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Case No. 59-1 Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties Donald W Geiger V Val Vs. Failure to Return to Active Status as Pilot, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Case No. 59-3 Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties Hoagland Vs. Val, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Case No. 59-4 Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties WE Schroeter ( Grievance Chairman) Vs. Val, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Case No. 59-5 Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties Fred C Welty Vs. United Air Lines, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 39)
- Personnel Files of F.C. Welty Discharge Case 59-5, 1958-1959 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- Case No. 59-9 Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties McKittrick Ham Van Almelo, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- Case No. 59-7 Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties Frank Salerno Vs. Val Inc., 1959 (Box 4, Folder 42)
- In the Matter of Investigation and hearing Regarding the Discharge of First Officer Earl A Shimon, United Air Lines, 1959 (Box 4, Folder 43)
- Sugar, Schwartz and Silver Attorneys at Law, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  Civil Action No: 32039
- Sugar, Schwartz and Silver Attorneys at Law, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  Civil Action No. 32039
- Case No. 66-9 United Air Lines Pilots System Bound of Adjustment In Matter of J.A. Young, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Case No 66-9 United Air Lines Pilots System Board of Adjustment In Matter of J.A. Young (Folder 1 of 2), 1967 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Case No. 66-9 United Air Lines Pilots System Board of Adjustment In Matters of J.A. Young, 1966-1967 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Before the United Air Lines Pilots System Board of Adjustment in the Matter of J.A. Young, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Young UAL Reply Brief, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Chronology 66-9, 1941-1965 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Before the United Air Lines Pilots System Board of Adjustment, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  In the Matter of J.A. Young
- FD 109, Sperry Greenwants Ex. # 17 + #18 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Case No. 66-9 J.A. Young, 1940-1965 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- United Air Lines Pilots System Board of Adjustment /, 1967-1967 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- United Air Lines Pilots System Board of Adjustment Decision in Grievance: Millard, Mulligan, Gates, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Before the United Air Lines Pilots System Board of Adjustment, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Before the United Air Lines Pilots System Board of Adjustment In Matter of Captain R.L. Trembley, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Before the United Air Lines Pilots System Board of Adjustment In re Grievance of R.L. Trembley, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Board No. 66-10 Hearing of R.L. Trembley, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Case No. 66-9 J.A. Young, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Horn 66-23, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Awaiting Hearing, 1967-1969 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Executive Session, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Ruling Motion to Dismiss Grievance of T.J. Vass + Decision in Grievance of J.C. Stear, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- United Air Lines Pilots System Board of Adjustment Board No. 68- 13- 68-14, 1969 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Personal File Decisions ET AL, 1959-1961 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Air Line Pilots Association Summary of Pilot Pension Plan Provisions, 1967 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Case No. 61-15 Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties Barton Duclos, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Case No. 61-16 Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties JL Brown, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Case No. 61-17 Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties Popham- Grout, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Case No. 61- 18 Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties: Wilson, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Case No. 61-19 Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties: H.B. Anders, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Case No. 62-20 Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties: Earl Moore Vs. Val, 1962-1963 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Case No. 61-20 Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties: Logan Vs. Val, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Casey 61-21, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Arnold et al Seniority 1961 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Case No. 62-1 Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties: Kremeier, 1961-1962 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- 62-12,13,14,16, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 11)
- ALPA 62-2 to 62-16, 1962-1963 (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Co Ex I to Co Ex VI, VII, IX, Assoc. Ex IV + VII, 1959-1961 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Duplicate of 62-11 thru 16, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- BD. Correspondence 1962 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Board No. 63-4 Decision in Grievance of Harlin E. Bell, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Carlson, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Harlin Bell 63-4, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Board Correspondence 1963, 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Vladek- Hyland 64-1, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- 64-29 (Folder 1 of 3) In the Matter of J.D. Clelland Vs. United Air Lines, Inc., 1965 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- 64-29, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- 64-29 Grievance Hearing of J.D. Clelland (Folder 3 of 3), 1964 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- ALPA Case No. 5651 In the Matter of T.M. Stretcher V. United Air Lines, Inc., 1964 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- ALPA To the UAL MEC, 1966 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Board Correspondence 1965 (Box 6, Folder 26)
- ALPA 65-2 3 and 5, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Arsenault 65-7, 1964-1965 (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Decision in Grievance of Dale R. Myers- Board No. 65-10, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- 65-11, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- United Air Lines Pilots System Board of Adjustment: Board Nos. 65-11,12,13 and 14, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 31)
- UP and CPA Brief and UP and CPA Reply Brief, 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- System Scheduling Committee Report and ALPA Case # 6202, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 33)
- ALPA Policy Manual and Negotiators Hand Book, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Rights and Duties of Air Carriers, Air Line Pilots Air Line Employees, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Constitution and By-Laws and The Laws of the Air Line Pilots, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 36)
- ALPA Letters (Various) + System Board of Adjustment Hearings- Order of Procedure, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Extra Copies, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Case No. Member File Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties: Clarence Savage Vs. VAL, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Case No. 60-1 (Member File) Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties: Earl A Shimon Vs. Val, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Case No. 60-2 (Member File) Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties: J.M. Sexton Vs. Val, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Case No. 60-3 (Member File) Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties: D.W. Howland Et AL Vs. V.A.L., 1960 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Case No. 60-4 (Member File) Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties: C. Savage Vs. V.A.l.., 1953-1960 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Case No. 60-5 (Member File) Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties: David Gardner Vs. VAL, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Case No. 60-6 (Member File) Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties: Warren Leroy (Acting MEC Chairman) Vs. VAL, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Case No. 60-7 (Member File) Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties: Charles B Carson Vs. VAL, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Case No. 60-8 (Member File) Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties: John R Cagney + J Stear Vs. VAL, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Case No. 60-9 (Member File) Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties: AW Schumann Vs. VAL, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Case No. 60-10 (Member File) Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties: G.S. Whitlock Vs. VAL, 1960-1961 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Case No. 60-11 Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties: P.K. Blais Vs. United Air Lines Inc. (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Board Correspondence 1961 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Extra Copies Misc., 1960 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Case No. 61-1 (Member File) Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties: W.R. Knight Vs. VAL Inc., 1961 (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Case No 61- 2 +61-3 Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties: B. Myers- A Kremeier, 1961-1961 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Case No. 61-4 Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties: Tassey, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Case No. 61-5 Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties: Lanedon, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Case No. 61-6 Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties: Wiseman, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Case No. 61-7 Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties: Rigsby Vs. VAL (Folder 1 of 6), 1961 (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Case No. 61-7 Air Line Pilots Association (International) Vs. Greenfleets- Annual Program Report (Folder 2 of 6), 1954 (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Case No. 61-7 Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties: Assoc. Ex VI (Folder 3 of 6) (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Case No. 61-7 Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties: Assoc Ex VII Vs. Capt. Reports (Folder 4 of 6), 1952 (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Pilot Instrument Proficiency Check Assoc. Ex VIII, IX, X, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Case No. 61-7 Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties: Rigsby Vs. VAL (Folder 6 of 6), 1954-1958 (Box 7, Folder 27)
- Case No. 61- 8 Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties: Coy Walden Vs. VAL (Folder 1 of 6), 1961 (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Case No. 61-8 Air Line Pilots Association (International) Ex 5 Capt. Reports (Walden), 1951 (Box 7, Folder 29)
- Case No. 61-8 Air Line Pilots Association (International) Ex 8 Green Sheets, 1952 (Box 7, Folder 30)
- Case No. 61-8 Air Line Pilots Association (International) Ex & Hood Checks (Folder 4 of 6), 1956 (Box 7, Folder 31)
- Case No. 61-8 Air Line Pilots Association (International) Ex 6 En Route Checks (Folder 5 of 6), 1952 (Box 7, Folder 32)
- Case No. 61-8 Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties: Coy Walden Vs. VAL (Folder 6 of 6), 1961 (Box 7, Folder 33)
- Case No. 61-9 Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties: Thomas, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 34)
- Case No. 61-10 Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties: McKittrick- Scroggs, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 35)
- Case No. 61-11 Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties: Anders, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 36)
- Case No. 61-12 Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties: Rennels, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 37)
- Case No. 61-13 Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties: Storey, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 38)
- Case No. 61-14 (Member File) Air Line Pilots Association (International) Parties: S.B. Wiper Vs. VAL INC., 1961 (Box 7, Folder 39)
- Board No. 69-1, 2 ,3, 4 68-1, 2,3,4,5, 8,12 67-7, 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- ALPA 69-4, 67-7, 1967-1969 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Lawrence 68-10, 68-16 RJ Miller Traynor 68-12 Travel 68-1 (2,3,4,5), 1969 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Kaintz et al 68-1 2,3,4,5, 7, 9 67-13-, 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Jx Traynor 67-10, 67-12, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- 1967 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- United Air Lines Pilots System Board of Adjustment Letters (Various), 1969 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- United Air Lines Pilots System Board of Adjustment + Mayer, Friedlichm Spiess, Tierney, Brown & Platt, 1967-1969 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- United Air Lines Pilots System Board of Adjustment + Board Case 66-9, 1966-1967 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- United Air Lines Pilots System Board of Adjustment- Grievance of J.A. Young and Trembley, 1966 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Powell 69-9 Pike 68-14 Moss 68-11 Williamson 68-6 RJ Miller68-15 Kincaid 68-17, 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Hunt 69-6 Co X 1-8 (Folder 1 of 5), 1969 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- 69-6 Assoc x A to Assoc. x V, 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- U.S. Naval Air Development Center A Dynamic Simulation Study of the Sweeping Transport Aircraft in Severe Turbulence, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 14)